Guide to the Kenneth Walter Cameron Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Kenneth Walter Cameron collection
1753-1947
GEN MSS 337
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
7.1
(11 boxes)
Collection includes: official seals of the United States, Canadian provinces, and the British Empire, primarily on letters from government officials laid into five scrapbooks; several magazines and an atlas of Canada; chart of Scottish clans and coats of arms; wax seals of Jersey (Channel Islands), Guernsey (Channel Islands), and Gambia Colony; collections of letters and autographs of literary, historical and church figures; zoology notebooks kept by Cameron while a student at West Virginia University; manuscript by Cameron entitled "The Channel Islands."
Other Storage Formats: Oversize, broadside cabinet
Cameron, Kenneth Walter, 1908-2006
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Kenneth Walter Cameron, 1937-1939.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Kenneth Walter Cameron, born in 1908, received his B.A. and M.A. degrees from West Virginia University in 1930 and 1931, an S.T.B. from General Theological Seminary, New York, in 1935, and his Ph.D. from Yale in 1940. He was ordained an Episcopal priest in 1935, and taught English at the University of North Carolina, Temple University and Trinity College. Cameron also served as archivist and historiographer of the Diocese of Connecticut.
Scope and Contents
The Kenneth Walter Cameron Collection consists of letters, documents and governmental seals collected by Cameron, as well as writings by Cameron himself. The collection is arranged into four series. Series I, Collection of Seals (1860-1947), consists of materials collected by Cameron for government and other seals, including five scrapbooks of autograph letters from United States and British government officials, three solid wax seals, several magazines and an atlas of Canada. Series II, Autograph Collection of Church Figures (1916-1939), contains Cameron's collection of manuscript, typewritten and printed documents and letters signed by clergy of the American, Anglican and Eastern Churches. Series III, Collection of Historic Documents (1753-1939), contains a collection of letters and documents signed by literary and historical figures of the 18th through 20th centuries. Series IV, Personal Papers (1927-1932), contains material written by Cameron. Oversize contains material from Series I and III.
Seals (Numismatics); Channel Islands -- History; Autographs (manuscripts); Scrapbooks; Seals; Clergy; Cameron, Kenneth Walter, 1908-2006
- Collection of Seals, 1860-1947; Series I; 0.1; (1/2 box)
  - INDIVIDUAL ITEMS
    - "Description of the [Cameron] Collection of Seals, Autographs, Original Covers bearing Postage, Stamps, and Gov't Documents", 1937 Apr 4
      Scope and Contents
      Signed by KWC
    - Printed material, 1946-47, n.d. (Box 1)
      Includes: Two brochures on the "British Commonwealth;" a copy of The National Geographic Magazine dated July, 1946; and a copy of Life magazine dated 1947 Aug 18
    - Dominion of Canada. Animated atlas, showing facsimiles of Canadian provincial seals on the cover. Text by Oliver Master, drawings by Arthur Edward Elias, [1926?]
    - Large Facsimile of the great seal of Puerto Rico, n.d.
    - "The Roll of the Highland Clans of Scotland," poster listing of Scottish clans and coats of arms
    - Seal of the United States General Land Office, on a certificate attached to a land grant to Dennis M. Smith, 1860, 1872
      The land grant is probably an official copy & was issued Oct. 1, 1860. The certificate is dated Aug. 16, 1872, and is signed by Willis Drummond, Commissioner of General Land Office. On the verso of the land grant is a certificate bearing the seal of the Circuit Court of Carter County, Missouri certifying that the papers are recorded there
    - Warranty deed given by James W. & Catherine M. Paxton to Christian Mabis of Wheeling, West Virginia, witnessed by Sam B. Huey & William Paxton, Jr., 1869 Apr 7 (Box 2)
      The seal of Samuel B. Huey, Commissioner of deeds is attached, and there is a note certifying that the deed is recorded, signed by R. B. Woods, Recorder
    - Official copy of a certificate of incorporation of the Wheeling and Bridgeport Ohio Railway Company, 1867 Oct 8
      For the purpose of building a street railroad. A certificate attesting this to be a true copy is attached. It is signed by the Secretary of State of Ohio, William Henry Smith, and bears the great seal of the state
  - WAX SEALS
    - Wax seal of Jersey, Channel Islands
    - Wax seal of Guernsey, Channel Islands [Broken in half]
    - Wax seal of Gambia Colony and Protectorate, bearing appended the autograph of the Governor and Commander-in-chief
  - SCRAPBOOKS
    Scrapbooks contain letters addressed to Cameron, collected for their signatures and seals
    - Volume I. Great seals of the states, territories, etc. of the United States, and of the provinces of the Dominion of Canada, 1924
      Together with postcard views of the state capitols, and autographs of governors and other public officials. Made by the Rev. K. W. Cameron in 1924
      Includes:
      Blan, S. H. TNS, Office of the Secretary of State, Montgomery, Alabama, 1 p., Feb. 7, 1924
      Baxter, Percival Proctor. TLS, Office of the Governor, Augusta, Maine, 1 p. with envelope, Feb. 16, 1924
      Cromwell, Emma Guy. TNS, Office of the Secretary of State, Frankfort, Kentucky, 1 p. with envelope, Jun. 12, 1924
      Hinkle, J. Grant. Typewritten note, signed, Office of the Secretary of State, Olympia, Washington, 1 p. with envelope, Apr. 1, 1924
      Hunt, George Wylie Paul. TLS, Office of the Governor, Phoenix, Arizona, 1 p. with envelope, Feb. 9, 1924
      Hunt, George Wylie Paul. Autograph signature, as Governor of Arizona, Jun. 26, 1924
      Kendall, Nathan E. TNS, Des Moines, Iowa, 1 p. with envelope, Mar. 31, 1924
      Mabey, Charles R. TNS, Salt Lake City, Utah, 1 p. with envelope, Feb. 26, 1924
      McCray, Warren T. TNS, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1 p. with envelope. Feb. 15, 1924
      McLeod, Thomas Gordon. TLS, Columbia, South Carolina, 1 p. with envelope, Apr. 7, 1924
      McMaster, William Henry. TNS, Pierre, South Dakota, 1 p. with envelope, Feb. 18, 1924
      Martin, Thomas F. TNS, Trenton, New Jersey, 1 p. with envelope, Mar. 28, 1924
      Parker, John Milliken. TNS, Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 1 p. with envelope, Feb. 21, 1924
      Silzer, George S. Autograph signature, on an engraved card, "State of New Jersey. Executive Department," with envelope, postmarked Jun. 21, 1924
      Trapp, Martin Edwin. TLS, Oklahoma City, 1 p. with envelope, Feb. 25, 1924
    - Volume II. Seals of the United States, British Empire, including the provinces of Canada and many colonial possessions, 1925-29
      Addison, D'Arcy Wentworth. TNS, Under Secretary's Office, Hobart, Tasmania, 1 p., Oct. 27, 1925
      Anderson, Maxwell Hendry. TLS, Colonial Secretary's Office, Gibralter, 1 p., Sep. 7, 1925
      Armitage, Cecil Hamilton. ALS, Government House, Bathurst, Gambia, 2 p., Feb. 26, 1926
      Barker, R. S. 2 TLS, New Brunswick, Sep. 4, 1926 (1 p.), Jan. 20, 1928 (1 p.)
      Barnstead, Arthur S. 3 TLS, Halifax, Nova Scotia, Aug. 27, 1925 (1 p.), Jan. 23, 1928 (1 p.), Feb. 4, 1928 (1 p.)
      Bayley, Benjamin Hamilton. TLS, Colonial Secretary's Office, Georgetown, Demerara, British Guiana, 1 p. with envelope, Oct. 10, 1925
      Baynes, Edward William. TLS, Colonial Secretary's Office, Antigua, Leeward Islands, 1 p. with envelope, Sep. 18, 1926
      Beattie, Liet.-Col. Alexander Elder. TNS, Colonial Secretary's Office, Stanley, Falkland Islands, 1 p. with envelope, Dec. 2, 1925
      Blinman, Harry. TNS, Chief Secretary's Office, Adelaide, South Australia, 1 p., Oct. 6, 1925
      Bolton, Horatio Norman. TNS, Peshawur, Northwest Frontier Province, India, 1 p. with envelope, Mar. 11, 1929
      Brownlee, J. E. TLS, Edmonton, Alberta, 1 p. with envelope, Sep. 3, 1926
      Burdon, John Alder. Signature, on a printed form for the Commission of a Deputy Governor, Belize, British Honduras, Jul. 13, 1925
      Copp, Arthur Bliss. TNS, Sackville, New Brunswick, 1 p. with envelope, Aug. 30, 1926
      Cordeaux, Harry Edward Spiller. TNS, Government House, Bahamas, 1 p. with envelope, Aug. 28, 1925
      Craik, Henry Duffield. TNS, Lahore, India, 1 p. with envelope, Nov. 30, 1926
      Douglas-Jones, Crawford. TNS, British Honduras, 1 p., Sep. 4, 1925
      Dutton, Eric Aldhelm Torlogh. TNS, Nairobi, Kenya, 1 p. with envelope, Dec. 24, 1926
      Eliot, Edward Carlyon. TNS, Government House, Dominica, 1 p. with envelope, Sep. 24, 1926
      Evans-Gordon, Kenmure Alick Garth. TNS, Bangalore, Coorg, India, 1 p. with envelope, Oct. 19, 1926
      Ferrar, Michael Lloyd. TNS, Andaman Islands, 1 p. with envelope, Oct. 16, 1925
      Finnie, O. B. TNS, Ottawa, Canada, 1 p. with envelope, Mar. 9, 1928
      Gaisford, Philip. TLS, Sibi, Baluchistan, India, 1 p. with envelope, Jan. 7, 1926
      Hailey, William Malcolm Hailey. Two signatures as Governor of Punjab, one an endorsement on a cancelled check, the other on a fragment of vellum, Nov. 22, 1926
      Hamilton, Eric William. TLS, Colonial Secretary's Office, Hongkong, 1 p. with envelope, Oct. 13, 1926
      Heape, William Leslie. TNS, The Secretariat, British Somaliland, 1 p. with envelope, Oct. 21, 1926
      Hutchings, Hugh H. TNS, Commissioner's Office, Grand Cayman, Cayman Islands, 1 p. with envelope, Oct. 1, 1926
      Hutchings, Robert Howell. TNS, Calcutta, Bengal, India, 1 p. with envelope, Oct. 19, 1925
      Johns, F. V. TNS, Toronto, Ontario, 1 p., May 17, 1929
      Kidson, Norman S. B. TNS, Tulagi, British Solomon Islands Protectorate, 1 p. with envelope, Jan. 14, 1926
      Lander, E. Lee. TNS, Ascension 19, 1925
      Leigh, A. H. C. Walker. TNS, Chief Commissioner's Office, Tamale, Northern Territories, Gold Coast, 1 p. with envelope, Sep. 19, 1927
      McLaren, John Gilbert. TNS, Melbourne, Australia, 1 p. with envelope, Aug. 20, 1926
      McLeod, J. W. TLS, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1 p. with envelope, Jan. 27, 1928
      Martin, Henry Robert Charles. 2 TLS, London, Aug. 16, 1926 (1 p.), Oct. 20, 1926 (1 p.)
      Maxwell, John. TNS, Kumasi, Ashanti, Gold Coast, 1 p. with envelope, Sep. 22, 1927
      Milner-White, Rudolph. TNS, Allabad, United Provinces, India, 1 p. with envelope, Nov. 30, 1925
      Mollett, Ralph. 5 ALS, Oct. 28, 1926 (Bailiff's Chambers, 1 p.), Apr. 11, 1927 (Royal Court, 3 p. folio), Aug. 24, 1927 (St. Helier, 2 p.), Feb. 3, 1928 (Jersey, 4 p.), Mar. 13, 1929 (Channel Islands, 3 p.), with envelopes
      Morrell, E. W. TLS, Jesselton, North Borneo, 1 p. with envelope, Oct. 25, 1926
      Mulvey, Thomas. 2 TLS, Ottawa, Canada, Sep. 9, 1926 (1 p. with envelope), Mar. 5, 1928 (1 p. with envelope)
      Mullan, Charles Seymour. TNS, Assam, India, 1 p. with envelope, Nov. 11, 1925
      Neill, James Scott. TNS, Suva, Fiji, 1 p. with envelope, Nov. 12, 1925
      Palmer, Harold L. TLS, Charlottetown, Prince Edward Island, 1 p. with envelope, Feb. 17, 1928
      Parker, Richard. TNS, Mount Abu, Ajmer-Merwara, India, 1 p. with envelope, Nov. 2, 1926
      Patterson, Stewart Blakely Agnew. Signature, as Agent to the Governor- General, Rajputana, India, n.d.
      Playford, E. Copley. TNS, Darwin, Australia, 1 p., Sep. 27, 1926
      Shapcott, Louis Edward. TLS, Perth, Australia, 1 p. with envelope, Oct. 15, 1925
      Sifton, James David. TLS, Ranchi, India, 1 p. with envelope, Oct. 14, 1925
      Simard, C. J. 2 TLS, Quebec, Canada, Jan. 26, 1928 (1 p. with envelope), Feb. 7, 1928 (1 p. with envelope)
      Smith, Conran. 2 TLS, Government House, Ootacamund, Madras, India, Oct. 8, 1925 (1 p.), Jul. 2, 1926 (1 p.)
      Starling, John Henry. TLS, Melbourne, 1 p. with envelope, Oct. 29, 1925
      Steward, Douglas Roy. TLS, Barbados, B. W. I., 1 p. with envelope, Sep. 1, 1927
      Stewart, H. R. TLS to Harold L. Palmer, Charlottetown, Prince Edward Island, 1 p., n.d.
      Storrs, Sir Ronald. ALS, Cyprus, 1 p. with envelope, Oct. 5, 1927
      Stubbs, Sir Reginald Edward. Signature, as Governor of Jamaica, Sep. 15, 1926
      White, J. L. TLS, Victoria, New Brunswick, 1 p., Jan. 20, 1928
      Wigley, Wilfrid Murray. TLS, St. Kitts, B. W. I., 1 p., Sep. 12, 1925
    - Volume III. Seals of the British Empire, and the United States (including many state seals), 1925-27
      Adams, William H. TNS, Denver, Colorado, 1 p., Jun. 21, 1927
      Bachmann, Carl George. 2 TLS, House of Representatives, Washington, Dec. 7, 1927 (1 p.), Dec. 11, 1927 (1 p.)
      Baker, Samuel A. Autograph of the governor and official seal of the state of Missouri, 1 p., n.d.
      Baldridge, H. Clarence. TLS, Office of the Governor, Boise, Idaho, 1 p., Jun. 23, 1927
      Balzar, Frederick Bennett. Autograph of the governor and official seal of the state of Nevada, 1 p., Aug. 9, 1927
      Bennett, John Robert. TLS, Colonial Secretary's Office, St. John's, Newfoundland, 1 p., Aug. 27, 1925
      Brewster, Ralph Owen. Autograph photograph of the governor and official seal of the state of Maine; with an engraved calling-card and an autographed post card
      Byrne, Sir Joseph Aloysius. Autograph, and official seal of Seychelles on sheet
      Carswell, George H. (Secretary of States, Georgia). TLS on stationary having the official seal of Georgia, 1 p., Sep. 12, 1928
      Champion, H. W. TLS, Port Moresby; This letter, written by the Government Secretary of Papua, is accompanied by the official seal of the territory, 1 p. with envelope, Oct. 15, 1925
      Christianson, Theodore. Autograph of the governor of Minnesota: facsimile, on sheet with two official seals, 1927
      Coghlan, Charles Patrick John. TLS, Cape Town, 1 p., Nov. 17, 1925
      Cox, Charles Henry Fortnom. TNS, Office of the Chief British Representative, Amman, Trans-Jordan, 1 p., Feb. 11, 1929
      Dillon, Richard Charles. Autograph of the Governor and official seals of the Territory od New Mexico and the state of New Mexico, 1 p., Jun. 22, 1927
      Donahey, A. Victor. Autograph of the governor and 3 seals of the state of Ohio, 3 p., Jun. 18, 1927
      Ellenberger, Lt.-Col. Jules. Autograph and official seal of the Resident Commissioner of the Bechuanaland Protectorate, 1 p.
      Erickson, John E. TNS, Helena, Montana, 1 p., Jun. 21, 1927
      Evans, Edward Walter. TNS, Mauritius, Oct. 16, 1925
      Farrington, Wallace Rider. TNS, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1 p., Aug. 22, 1927
      Fields, William Jason. 2 autographs of the governor and 2 official seals of the state of Kentucky, Nov. 17, 1927
      Fisher, John S. Autograph of the governor and official seals of the state of Pennsylvania, 1 p., n.d.
      Fuller, Alvan Tufts. Autograph of the governor of Massachusetts on a calling card; Accompanied by a TLS from Franklin Delano Putnam, Department of the Attorney General, Boston, Mass., 1 p., June 30, 1927
      Graves, Bibb. TLS, Executive Department, Montgomery, Alabama, 1 p., Aug. 12, 1927
      Green, Frederick Warren. TLS, Executive Office, Lansing, Michigan, Aug. 10, 1927
      Griffith, T. (Administrator of Nauru). TLS, Nauru, 1 p. with envelope, Nov. 10, 1925
      Grindle, Gilbert Edmund Augustine. TNS, Colonial Office, London, 1 p., Nov. 16, 1926
      Hammill, John. Autograph of the governor and seal of the state of Iowa, 1 p., Jun. 20, 1927
      Hancock, Otho Lewis. TLS, Commissioner's Office, Tortola, Virgin Islands, Sep. 3, 1925
      Hardman, Lamartine Griffin. TLS, Executive Department, Atlanta, 1 p., May 31, 1928
      Harper, Sir Charles Henry. Autograph and official seal on sheet
      Higgins, Jim B. (Secretary of State, Arkansas). TLS, with official seal of the state of Arkansas, Little Rock, 1 p., Jan. 16, 1928
      Hughes, John Whitehouse Ward. ALS, Keene, New Hampshire, 1 p., Nov. 9, 1925
      Jackson, Ed. TLS, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1 p., Jun. 20, 1927
      Jarvis, Edward Blockwell. TNS, Entebbe, Uganda, 1 p., Sep. 26, 1925
      Johnston, Henry S. (Governor of Oklahoma). Autograph of the governor and official seal of the state of Oklahoma, 1 p., n.d.
      Lee, Frank Charles. 2 TLS, Singapore, Straits Settlements, Apr. 30 1928 (1 p.), Apr 12, 1929 (1 p.)
      McLean, Angus Wilton. Autograph of the governor and official seal of the state of North Carolina, 2 p., Jun. 24, 1927
      McMullen, Adam. Autograph and governor's seal, and official seal of the state of Nebraska, 1 p., n.d.
      McOwan, Islay. TLS, Consulate, Tonga, Friendly Islands, 1 p., Nov. 25, 1925
      Martin, John Wellborn. TNS, Tallahassee, 1 p., Aug. 8, 1927
      Martineau, John Ellis. 2 TNS, Little Rock, Arkansas, Sep. 6, 1927 (1 p.), Jan. 9, 1928 (1 p.)
      Moore, Arthur Henry. Autograph and seal of the governor and official seal of the state of New Jersey, 1 p., n.d.
      Murphree, Dennis. Autograph of the official seal of the state of Mississippi, 1 p., n.d.
      Parks, George Alexander. Autograph of the governor, on calling card, and official seal, on small sheet of paper, of the Territory of Alaska, [Jan. 21, 1928]
      Patterson, Isaac Lee (Governor of Oregon). Autograph of the governor and official seal of the state of Oregon, n.d.
      Paulen, Ben Sandford. Autograph of the governor and official seal of the state of Kansas, 1 p. and card, [1927?]
      Plowman, George Thomas. TNS, Administrator's Office, Natal, 1 p., Oct. 7, 1925
      Plunkett, Oliver. TLS, Saint Lucia, 1 p., Feb. 4, 1927
      Pothier, Aram J. Autograph of the governor and official seal of the state of Rhode Island, 1 p., [Aug. 10, 1927]
      Rankine, Richard Sims Donkin. TLS, Zomba, Nyasaland Protectorate, 1 p., Oct. 1, 1925
      Richards, John G. Autograph and seal of the governor and official seal of the state of South Carolina, 1 p., n.d.
      Ritchie, Albert Cabell. TLS, Annapolis, Maryland, 1 p., Jun. 18, 1927
      Robinson, Robert P. TNS, Dover, Delaware, 1 p., Jun. 24, 1927
      Shapley, L. S. (Governor of Guam). Autograph and official seal of the government of Guam, [Sep. 10, 1927]
      Smith, Alfred Emanuel. 2 Autographs of the governor and the Executive Privy Seal of the state of New York, 1 p. and card, Jun. 28, 1927
      Smith-Rewse, Geoffrey Whistler Bingham. TLS, British Residency, Vila, New Hebrides, 1 p., Dec. 9, 1925
      Sorlie, Arthur Gustav. Autograph of the Governor and official seal of the state of North Dakota, 1 p., Sep. 7, 1927
      Spaulding, Huntley Nowel. TLS, Concord, N. H., 1 p., Aug. 9, 1927
      Southard, Addison E. TLS, Singapore, 1 p., Dec. 28, 1927
      Towner, Horace Mann. TLS, Autograph correpondence card, and official seal, Porto Rico, 1 p., Feb. 28, 1928
      Trumbull, John N. Autograph on calling card, with the official seal of the state, n.d.
      Walker, Meriwether Lewis. TLS, Balboa, Panama, 1 p., Aug. 17, 1927
      Walter, Robert. 2 TLS, St. Vincent, B. W. I., Sep. 25, 1925 (1 p.), Aug. 30, 1927 (1 p.)
      Washington D. C. Commissioners. Sheet of official stationary containing the official seal and the autographs of the following commissioners of the District of Columbia: Proctor L. Dougherty, Sidney F. Taliaferro, and W. E. R. Covell, Washington, 1 p., [Jun. 24, 1927]
      Williams, Philip Stanhope. TLS, Perlis, Malay States, Aug. 27, 1926
      Wisdom, Evan A. TLS, Rabaul, New Guinea, Nov. 27, 1927
      Wood, Leonard. Autograph of the Governor General and official seal of the Philippine Islands, 1 p., Oct. 18, 1926
    - Volume IV. Seals of the United States (including state and departmental seals), seals of various consulates both here and abroad, and some seals of British colonial possessions, 1925-37
      Aaltio, Kaarlo Fredrik. TLS, New York, 1 p., Sep. 6, 1927
      Adams, Charles Francis. TNS, Department of the Navy, Washington, D. C., 1 p., Jun. 27, 1929
      Assal, A. F. Bey, TLS, Consul of Egypt, 1 p., Aug. 24, 1937
      Axerio, Emilio. 2 TLS, Sep. 8, 1927 (Consalato d'Italia, 1 p.), Sep. 24, 1927 (Cleveland, Ohio, 1 p.)
      Beard, Mrs. Cyrus. TLS, Dept. of History, Cheyenne, Wyoming, 1 p., Apr. 2, 1928
      Bliss, Robert Woods. TNS, Embassy of the United States, Buenos Aires, 1 p., Sep. 13, 1927
      Bonilla, M. A. (Consul General of Costa Rica). TLS, Enclosing the official seal of the Consulado General de Costa Rica en Nueva York), 1 p., Sep. 8, 1927
      Brooke, Charles Vyner, His Highness, Rajah of Sarawak. 2 Autograph signatures, with State Seals of Sarawak, n.d.
      Bulow, William John. TNS, South Dakota, 1 p., Jun. 21, 1927
      Byrd, Harry Flood. Autograph, n.d.
      Chiriboga, B. (In 1927 Señor Chiriboga was Acting Consul General of Ecuador in New York). TLS, New York, 1 p., Aug. 25, 1927
      Curtis, R. J. TLS, Office of the British Resident, Brunei, Borneo, 1 p., Apr. 5, 1929
      Dern, George Henry. 2 TNS, Salt Lake City, Utah, Jun. 20, Jun. 21, 1927
      Donnelly, Frederick William. Autograph signature as Mayor of the City of Trenton, New Jersey, 1 p. with envelope, [May 29, 1928]
      Drechsler, R. Walther. TLS, New York, 1 p. with envelope, Sep. 16, 1927
      Drutzu, Serban. TLS, Royal Consulate General of Roumania, 1 p. with envelope, Aug. 24, 1927
      Elias, Arturo M. TLS, New York City, 1 p. with envelope, Aug. 29, 1927
      Emerson, Frank C. Autograph signature, as Governor of Wyoming, Cheyenne, Wyoming, 1 p., [1929?]
      Evans, Waldo. TLS, St. Thomas, Virgin Islands, Feb. 4, 1928
      Farfan, J. M. TLS, Trinidad, 1 p. with envelope, Jan. 22, 1929
      Faurie, A. M. Autograph signature, [Cape Town], 1 p., [1925?]
      Freyer, F. B. TLS, Washington, 1 p., May 3, 1929
      Gompers, Samuel J. 2 TLS, Office of the chief clerk, Dept. of labor, Washington, D. C. Aug 21, 1926 (1 p.), Sep. 1, 1926 (1 p.)
      Goodwin, Thomas Herbert John Chapman. TNS, Queensland, 1 p., Feb. 25, 1929
      Gore, Howard Mason. ANS with the seal of West Virginia, Executive Department, Charleston, West Virginia, 1 p., Oct. 12, 1927
      Gregg, Jacob. TLS, Royal Norwegian Consulate General, New York, 1 p. with envelope, Aug. 24, 1921
      Gruszka, Sylvester. TLS, Consulate General of Poland, New York City, Aug. 25, 1927
      Hartley, Roland H. 2 TNS, Executive Department, Olympia, Washington (With the seal of the state of Washington), Jun. 22, 1927 (1 p.), Sep. 7, 1927 (1 p.)
      Higginson, Eduardo. TLS, Consulate General of Peru, New York City, 1 p., Aug. 25, 1927
      Hinkle, J. Grant. TLS, Department of State, Olympia, Washington, 1 p., Mar. 29, 1928
      Jardine, William Marion. Autograph signature, as Secretary of Agriculture, [Washington, D. C.], 1 p., [Aug. 23, 1926]
      La Vega, Emeterio Cano de. TLS, Consulado général de Bolivia, New York City, 1 p., Sep. 1, 1927
      Lee, Frank Charles. TLS, Singapore, 1 p., Feb 7, 1929
      Mongendre, Maxime Anatole Aristide. TLS, Consulat général de France à New York, 1 p., Aug. 24, 1927
      Moody, Dan. Autograph signature, as Governor of Texas, Execuative Dept., Austin, Texas, 1 p., [Jun. 1927?]
      Nicholson, Bertram. TNS, Mbabane, Swaziland, 1 p., Feb. 14, 1929
      Oakes, Charles William. ALS, "Quandong" Balfour Rd., Woollahra, N. S. W., 1 p., Sep. 30, 1925
      Pacheco, Pablo A. TNS, with the seal of the Consulado General de la Republica Argentina, New York, 1 p., Aug. 24, 1927
      Prifti, George N. ALS, Boston, Mass., 1 p., Aug. 17, 1927
      Samuel, Edwin. TLS, Jerusalem, 1 p. with envelope, Feb. 28, 1929
      Stimson, Henry Lewis. Autograph signature, [Washington, D. C., May 3, 1929]
      Todorovitch, George V. TLS, New York, 1 p., Aug. 29, 1927
      Valencia, Gabriel (Consul General of Columbia). TLS, with the official seal, New York, Aug. 20, 1927
      Washburn, Albert Henry. TLS, Vienna, 1 p., Aug. 31, 1927
      Weeks, John Eliakim. Autograph signature, as Governor of Vermont, [Montpellier, Vt. Jun? 1927]